export default {
  main: [
//     {
//       question: "Need help convincing your manager? ",
//       answer: `Need help getting approval to attend the Nextflow Summit? We’ve got you covered.<br><br> To make it easier to explain the benefits of attending, we’ve prepared a template letter for you. Just edit it to suit your needs and make your case. Take the first step toward joining us—download the template now and secure your spot! <a href="https://docs.google.com/document/d/10IoOqcCn93PhR4LwF_A_tXx40iCjOEBWKGyqb5FHVvw/edit?tab=t.0">Download the template </a>
// `,
//     },
{
  question: "How do I register for the Nextflow Training and nf-core Hackathon Barcelona 2025?",
  answer:
  `<p>To register for Nextflow Training Barcelona 2025, click <a href="https://seqera.swoogo.com/nextflow-training" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>
  <p>To register for the nf-core Hackathon Barcelona 2025, click <a href="https://seqera.swoogo.com/nfcore-hackathon" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>`,
},
    {
      question: "How do I register for Nextflow Summit?",
      answer:  
         `<p>Register and attend for free by clicking <a href="https://seqera.registration.goldcast.io/events/dc611bf3-ddc4-4a20-9f2f-1a9e941cc68c" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>`
    },
    {
      question: "How much are the registration fees?",
      answer:
        `<p>Early-bird 25% discount available until August 1.</p>
        
        <p>   <span class="underline">Nextflow Training (Barcelona)</span><br/>
             Academic: <s>€120</s> €90  <br/>
             Corporate: <s>€300</s> €225 
          </p>
          <p>
          <span class="underline">nf-core Hackathon (Barcelona)</span><br/>
          Academic: <s>€120</s> €90<br/>
          Corporate <s>€120</s> €90<br/>

          <p>
          <p>
          <span class="underline">Nextflow Summit (Virtual)</span><br/>
            Free
          </p>
          `
  },
  {
    question: "What is included in the registration fee for Nextflow Training and nf-core Hackathon?",
    answer:
      `Your ticket includes:
        <ul>
        <li>Access to all in-person content and programming</li>
        <li>Enjoy meals and social events</li>
        <li>Network and connect with other attendees</li>
        </ul>
        `
  },
  {
    question: "Are there discounts for group registration?",
    answer:
      `Contact our team at <a href="mailto:help.summit@nextflow.io">help.summit@nextflow.io</a> to inquire about group registrations.`
  },
  {
    question: "Are there student discounts or financial assistance available?",
    answer:
      `<p>Accessibility is important to us. We strive to make the event affordable and available to the community. If you are interested in attending and registration cost is a barrier, please reach out to <a href="mailto:help.summit@nextflow.io">help.summit@nextflow.io</a> to discuss sliding scale discounts.</p>`
},
  {
    question: "Why is Nextflow Summit virtual?",
    answer:
      `<p>Nextflow Summit wants to spotlight more amazing community talks and make it easier for people everywhere to take part. </p>
      <p>With in-person time for connection and collaboration in Barcelona, and online talks to reach a global audience, this format brings the best of both worlds.</p>`
  },
    {
      question: "Are there recommended hotels near the Training & Hackathon venue?",
      answer: `<p>Please see the <a href="/2025/barcelona/travel">Travel</a> page for hotel recommendations near the Barcelona venue.</p>`,
    },
    // {
    //   question:
    //     "Who typically attends the summit, and what networking opportunities are available?",
    //   answer:
    //     "Data scientists, bioinformaticians, computational biologists as well as heads of data, CIOs, CTOs",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "What skills or knowledge can I expect to gain by attending?",
    //   answer: `
    //         <p><ul>By attending the Summit you will get to:</p> 
    //         <ul>
    //     <li>Take training which will equip you with the skills to build better pipelines.</li>
    //     <li>Participate in the hands-on Hackathon to solve real-world challenges and develop advanced pipelines.</li>
    //     <li>Gain insights from scientific talks, keynotes, and panel discussions.</li>
    //     <li>Present your project, receive community feedback, and identify optimization opportunities.</li>
    //    <li>Build connections with industry leaders, experts, and the broader Nextflow community.</li>
    //     </ul>`,
    // },
    // {
    //   question:
    //     "Will there be opportunities to interact with Nextflow experts and developers?",
    //   answer: "Yes, you'll have the chance to connect with top experts across multiple event tracks throughout the action-packed days!",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "What are the key topics and themes covered during the Summit?",
    //   answer: `<p>This year the Boston Summit will cover the following themes Enabling Science, Big Nextflow, and Organizational Impact.</p> 
    //   <p>More information on the Barcelona Summit coming soon.</p>`,
    // },
  ],
};
